const STORE = [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'Which philosopher said, "I think, therefore I am"?',
      answers: ['Aristotle', 'Immanuel Kant', 'Rene Descartes', 'Socrates'],
      correctAnswer: 'Rene Descartes'
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'Which philosopher championed the "Theory of Forms” or “Ideas"?',
      answers: ['Aristotle', 'Augustine of Hippo', 'Confucius', 'Plato'],
      correctAnswer: 'Plato'
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'Which philosopher is considered the “Father of Logic”?',
      answers: ['Aristotle', 'Immanuel Kant', 'Isaac Newton', 'Pythagoras'],
      correctAnswer: 'Aristotle'
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'Which philosopher said, “It is better to be a human being dissatisfied than a pig satisfied; better to be Socrates dissatisfied than a fool satisfied.”?',
      answers: ['Homer', 'John Stuart Mill', 'Plato', 'Thomas Aquinas'],
      correctAnswer: 'John Stuart Mill'
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'Which philosopher focused most of his work on integrating Aristotelian thought with Christian doctrine?',
      answers: ['Augustine of Hippo', 'Bonaventure', 'Duns Scotus', 'Thomas Aquinas'],
      correctAnswer: 'Thomas Aquinas'
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'Which philosopher defined the “categorical imperative"?',
      answers: ['Confucius', 'David Hume', 'Friedrich Nietzsche', 'Immanuel Kant'],
      correctAnswer: 'Immanuel Kant'
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'Which philosopher proclaimed that “God is dead”?',
      answers: ['Albert Camus', 'David Hume', 'Friedrich Nietzsche', 'Thomas Hobbes'],
      correctAnswer: 'Friedrich Nietzsche'
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'Which philosopher was a proponent of “idealism,” the view that reality consists exclusively of minds and their ideas?',
      answers: ['Baruch Spinoza', 'David Hume', 'George Berkeley', 'John Locke'],
      correctAnswer: 'George Berkeley'
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Which philosopher argued that, with regard to motivation to act morally, “Reason is, and ought only to be the slave of the passions”?',
      answers: ['Bertrand Russell', 'David Hume', 'Jean-Jacques Rousseau', 'Karl Marx'],
      correctAnswer: 'David Hume'
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'Which philosopher said that “The unexamined life is not worth living”?',
      answers: ['Aristotle', 'Ludwig Wittgenstein', 'Socrates', 'Soren Kierkegaard'],
      correctAnswer: 'Socrates'
    }
  ];